Hello Hello Everyone Today we will give you a review of Tata AIG
General Insurance Company's accident
plan. Our
subscribers were requested to
review this plan.
Before appointing us, we should give some information about accidents. According to that, please
subscribe in India and in every
country, you must definitely do it for yourself in case of accidents.
Very
grateful to subscribe. If you
decide to subscribe, then if a
brave warrior goes missing in a war, then
after a waiting period of one year,
whatever amount is related to the policy holder is given to the nominee. The
second benefit is Permanent Total
Disability. If the policy holder becomes
permanently disabled due to an accident,
then whatever amount is given to the policy holder is given. It
means that the policy
holder is not in a working position,
due to this, there is an
account in the middle and whoever you select, you
get the shoulder according to the list.
If
you use it, then the one you
get from it is soft and the best protein
maximum.  I am putting it on you, you can check how much
you will get in what thing, how much time in this situation
Next
Benefits Punishment Total Disability If the
policy holder's temperature drops due to an accident, the maximum amount
subscribed to this plan can be 104
which can be
and the maximum amount
less than ₹50 is the benefit to the policy holder
Accident Hospitalization
If the policy holder has to be
admitted to the hospital due to an accident, then the company works in the company
and the
maximum amount can be up to 5 lakhs,
whichever is less out of these will fall on the company Defaulters
Admission to the policy holder is compulsory
Next Benefits Punishment Hospitalization
If the policy holder is admitted to the hospital
due to an accident, then the company works in the
company and the maximum amount less than ₹50 is the benefit to the policy holder Maximum limit
for the benefit of the company hospitalization is
6 Days
If the policy holder is admitted to the hospital due to an accident, then the
company will pay a maximum of ₹5000 to the policy holder If this
condition happens then
her husband will be  The policy
holder should
subscribe to the
benefits. This means that if the policy holder
dies due to an accident, then the company
also pays the money spent on this plan on the
claim, which can be one per cent
of the minimum and the
company will pay a maximum of Rs. 25,000. Next:
Ambulance cost in a plane:
If the policy holder is hospitalized due to an accident, then the
company pays the
ambulance fare up to a maximum limit of Rs. 25,000.
Air ambulance is also included in this plan.
If the policy holder
requires an air ambulance due to an accident, then the company will pay the
repair up to a maximum limit of Rs. 5 lakh.
Next: Benefits: Cost of car,
wheelchair and wheelchair: If the company clears the claim, then
in the situation of permanent total disability, the company pays 10 percent for other necessary benefits for the wheel chair
and a maximum of Rs. 1 lakh for the
claim. Next
Benefits include the cost of
artificial limbs. If the policyholder
requires artificial limbs due to an accident, the company waives the cost,
which can be ten percent of the premium and a
maximum of Rs 1 lakh.
You can also add option features to this plan,
like child tuition benefit. If the
policyholder dies due to an accident
and the child is less than one year old, the
company will waive the tuition fee for the child
and a benefit of up to Rs 1 lakh
on the claim. Software benefit
is a loan. If the policyholder
dies due to an accident, the
company will waive twenty-five percent of the premium, which can be
used to protect the loan.
These are optional benefits, for which you will have to make an
additional payment. Accidental
also has some exclusions, which we are putting on the screen,
you can check them, like
drink and drive or any other like drink
and drive suicide attempt to itself.  If the
policy holder tries to cause injury, then
in that situation Ford company does
not entertain the claim. Android user quality,
stress and depression and there are many other reasons
which can be the reason for claim reaction.
This is the benefit of Tata Magic Accidental Policy
which is very good. If
you feel that you have not subscribed, then there is a
free look period,
we keep bringing updated information about the feed subscription, so
please like and subscribe our channel.
Thank you for watching.
[Sangeet]